opiumpulses.com 2017-11-28

# Opium Pulses - Privacy

This privacy policy sets out how opiumpulses.com uses and protects any information that you give opiumpulses.com when you use this website. opiumpulses.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. opiumpulses.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**Information Collected**

  * Email address
  * IP address and location
  * Device fingerprint
  * Ecommerce order details
  * Activity details and history
  * Connections between users and how they are linked
  * Optional profile information including a bio and account links to social media and gaming profiles

**How We Use Your Information**

We require this information mostly to protect you and prevent fraudulent activity on our site.

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing information to you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

**Cookies**

Our site uses cookies for collecting data, and to enhance our service. We also use Google Analytics to help understand how users engage with our website.

To learn more about the data Google collects and processes, please visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
